<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Animalspedia</string>
    <string name="pilih_gambar">(Select image to open gallery)</string>
    <string name="daftar_ras_judul">" Animal Race List"</string>
    <string name="ayam">Chicken</string>
    <string name="anjing_list_title">Dog Race List</string>
    <string name="ayam_list_title">Dog Race List</string>
    <string name="buaya">Crocodile</string>
    <string name="kucing">Cat</string>
    <string name="buaya_list_title">Crocodile Race List</string>
    <string name="kucing_list_title">Cat Race List</string>
    <string name="Pomeranian_nama">Pomeranian</string>
    <string name="Pomeranian_asal">Africa</string>
    <string name="Pomeranian_deskripsi">This one dog is very cute isn\'t it? Its small body and thick fur like pom-poms, make it a favorite pet of many people. At first glance, the Pomeranian looks like a doll, so it\'s not uncommon for owners to dress this cute dog in clothes. This dog is known to be spoiled and loyal. In fact, when you only go to the toilet for a while, he could be waiting for you at the door. Funny, isn\'t it?</string>
    <string name="Poodle_nama">Poodle</string>
    <string name="Poodle_asal">eastern europe</string>
    <string name="Poodle_deskripsi">Poodle dogs have a characteristic, namely the curly fur. If the fur grows thick, then he will look elegant and very cute. In addition, poodles are also known as intelligent dogs. So, it is very easy for him to train.</string>
    <string name="Shih_tzu_nama">Shih tzu</string>
    <string name="Shih_tzu_asal">Japan</string>
    <string name="Shih_tzu_deskripsi">" Shih tzu dogs have fine hair that can grow long. So, you can tie it like a girl's hair. Because of its beautiful fur, this dog is often entered into dog beauty contests. Shih tzu is also a friendly and sociable dog. "</string>
    <string name="Maltese_nama">Maltese</string>
    <string name="Maltese_asal">America</string>
    <string name="Maltese_deskripsi">Maltese dogs have very fine fur and round eyes. The advantage of keeping this dog is that the hair does not fall out easily.</string>
    <string name="Pekingese_nama">Pekingese</string>
    <string name="Pekingese_asal">Europe</string>
    <string name="Pekingese_deskripsi">Although it looks small, who would have thought that this type of dog is muscular and quite heavy. Its thick fur, makes the pekingese look like a walking cloud.</string>
    <string name="Beagle_nama">Beagle</string>
    <string name="Beagle_asal">Maxico</string>
    <string name="Beagle_deskripsi">"The beagle is a bloodhound because it has a sharp sense of smell and a muscular body. However, because of their small size, this dog will look very cute. "</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cochin_nama">Cochin Chiken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cochin_asal">Chinese</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cochin_deskripsi">The most visible characteristic of the cochin chicken is the number of feathers on the legs. This chicken was originally a chicken from China, but the people who breed it are all over the world. These chickens can find their own food and are not too difficult to care for.</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Kelabu_nama">Gray Jungle Chiken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Kelabu_asal">Asia</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Kelabu_deskripsi">This chicken has another name Gallus Sonneratii. The male gray jungle fowl generally has a length of about 80 cm. It has black and white speckled neck and nape hair. The legs have a color between bright reddish yellow. Some types of gray jungle fowl have purplish black tails.</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Kapas_nama">Cotton Chicken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Kapas_asal">Brazil</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Kapas_deskripsi">Cotton chicken. At first glance, you will not think that this animal is a chicken. His fur that was as white as cotton made him at first glance look like a poodle. It is not clear where this chicken came from, but it is thought to have come from China. It has a crest that leads to the back of the body.</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Orpington_nama">Orpington Chiken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Orpington_asal">France</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Orpington_deskripsi">This chicken is the result of a cross between the Plymouth Rock and the Minorca. This chicken has a characteristic large body and the ability to quickly produce eggs. It also has very fine looking fur. Because this chicken is the result of a successful cross, the Orpington chicken is easy to breed.</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Merah_nama">Red Jungle Chiken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Merah_asal">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Hutan_Merah_deskripsi">Red Jungle Chicken is also included in one of the original chickens from the Indonesian jungle. The weight is quite light, the rooster is usually only 700 grams, while the hen is only 400 grams. This chicken is often used as a pet at home.</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cemani_nama">Cemani Chiken</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cemani_asal">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="Ayam_Cemani_deskripsi">Cemani chicken is one of the chickens originating from Indonesia. Unlike other types of chicken, cemani chicken only has black color.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Orinoco_nama">Orinco Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Orinoco_asal">America</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Orinoco_deskripsi">The Orinoco crocodile is a species of large crocodile with a relatively elongated snout and a pale brown color with scattered dark brown markings. They mainly live in the Orinoco Basin. Despite having a rather narrow snout, they prey on a wide variety of vertebrates, including large mammals. The Orinoco crocodile is an endangered species.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Air_Tawar_nama">Freshwater Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Air_Tawar_asal">Australia</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Air_Tawar_deskripsi">The freshwater crocodile is a small species with a narrow, elongated snout. They are light brown in color with darker bands on the body and tail. These crocodiles live in rivers far enough from the sea to avoid confrontation with estuarine crocodiles. They mostly eat fish and other small vertebrates.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Filipina_nama">Filipina Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Filipina_asal">Filipina</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Filipina_deskripsi">The Philippine crocodile is a relatively small species with a rather broad snout. They have heavy dorsal skin and a golden brown color that darkens as they mature. These crocodiles prefer freshwater habitats and feed on a variety of small to medium-sized vertebrates. Apart from being Endangered, the Philippine Crocodile is also the most threatened species of crocodile.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Morelet_nama">Morelat Buaya</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Morelet_asal">Maxico</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Morelet_deskripsi">Also known as the Mexican alligator, this reptile is small to medium in size with a slightly broad snout. They have a dark grayish brown coloration and are found in mostly a variety of freshwater habitats. They eat mammals, birds and reptiles. Mexican Crocodile is listed as Low Risk.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Nill_nama">Nill Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Nill_asal">Africa</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Nill_deskripsi">The Nile crocodile is a large and aggressive species with a large snout, especially in older animals. They have a dark bronze color and darken as they mature. They live in a variety of freshwater habitats, but can also be found in brackish water. Nile crocodiles are apex predators capable of preying on a wide variety of African vertebrates, including ungulates and other large predators. This species is listed as Low Risk.</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Irian_nama">Irian Crocodile</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Irian_asal">Indonesia</string>
    <string name="Buaya_Irian_deskripsi">The Irian Crocodile is a species of small crocodile with a gray-brown coloration and brown to black markings on the tail. Young crocodiles have a V-shaped snout that is narrower and wider as they mature. They prefer freshwater habitats, although they are also tolerant of saltwater, to avoid competition and predation by estuarine crocodiles. This species feeds on small to medium-sized vertebrates.</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Persia_nama">Persian cat</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Persia_asal">Iran</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Persia_deskripsi">The Persian cat is one of the most popular domestic cats in many countries around the world. They came from Persia (present-day Iran). The first records of the existence of Persian cats date back to the 17th century.</string>
    <string name="Kucing_British_Shorthair_nama">British Shorthair cat</string>
    <string name="Kucing_British_Shorthair_asal">" American continent"</string>
    <string name="Kucing_British_Shorthair_deskripsi">The British Shorthair or also known as the British Blue is one of the cutest and most popular pet cats. With a distinctive chunky body, broad face shape and thick fur coat, the British Shorthair is also the inspiration for the famous Cheshire Cat from the film Alice in Wonderland.</string>
    <string name="Maine_Coon_nama">" Maine Coon Cat"</string>
    <string name="Maine_Coon_asal">America</string>
    <string name="Maine_Coon_deskripsi">This giant cat is native to the State of Maine, United States, and is one of the oldest natural breeds in North America. Maine Coons are very welcoming and friendly despite their fierce appearance; that\'s why they are dubbed the \"gentle giant.\"</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Siam_nama">Siam Cat</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Siam_asal">Chinese</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Siam_deskripsi">This cat is very tolerant, calm and friendly. They really adore their owners. Not surprisingly, their distinctive appearance has inspired the creation of several new cat breeds, one of which is the Ocicat.</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Bengal_nama">Bengal Cat</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Bengal_asal">Australia</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Bengal_deskripsi">These lovely cats love to climb and jump, they are very active and playful. Bengal cats require frequent social interactions with their owners and they shed hair less frequently.</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Manx_nama">Manx Cat</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Manx_asal">Southeast Asia</string>
    <string name="Kucing_Manx_deskripsi">Manx cats are native to the Isle of Man and are well known for their tailless genes. Some Manx cats have no tail at all, while others can have half the length of a standard cat\'s tail. The Manx has been recognized by many cat registries since the late 19th century.</string>
    <string name="go_back">Return</string>
    <string name="anjing">Dog</string>
</resources>